filmygyan.co 2016-03-15

# Filmygyan | Policysdsad

**Privacy on Filmygyan**

We at **Filmygyan** respect the privacy of our users and of those who visit anonymously to the website. We want to let you know that how your personal data or information is being used by Filmygyan.

If you are less than 18 years please get an adult or above 18 to help you to understand or ask us to explain it.

Here are some of the things we cover:

* Collecting information from you

* Using the information that we collect

* The ways you can access and change your information

* How we keep your information safe

 **Information we receive and how it is used:**

We receive a number of different types of information about you, including:

* nbsp; **Your information**

Your information is the information that's required when you sign up for the site, as well as the information you choose to share.

 **Registration information:**

When you sign up for Filmygyan, you are required to provide information such as your name, email address, birthday, and gender. In some cases, you may be able to register using other information, like your telephone number.

User availing services on Filmygyan via other social networking websites allows us to obtain information like User’s Email ID, Contacts, Friends etc. By accessing our app and giving any information, user gives us permission to use information for business purpose.

 **Information you choose to share:**

Your information also includes the information you choose to share on Filmygyan, such as you post a Question, Bio, Status, Upload a photo or Comment on a story, your data is passed on to the site. It also includes the information you choose to share when you communicate with us, such as when you contact us using an email address, or when you take an action, such as when you follow friend, like a Movie Page, use our contact importers, or indicate you are in a relationship.

 **Information about friends, connections and contacts:**

You can choose to invite your friends to join Filmygyan, so that you can stay in touch with them on the site. To make it easier to search and find friends and people you know on Filmygyan, users may search for other members using first and last name, email address and location. If you want to invite your friends and contacts to become a Filmygyan member, we will send an email or an SMS invitation from Filmygyan in your name to your friends and contacts, encouraging them to sign up to Filmygyan.

If any of the people you've invited don't register within a few days, Filmygyan may occasionally send reminder emails or an SMS on your behalf to those individuals. You can choose to invite all your friends or only a select few by simply un-ticking the names of those friends you don't want to invite. It's up to you to ensure that your friends are happy to receive your Filmygyan invite. Otherwise, the only information we hold about your friends and contacts is what you tell us through the site. So, again, think carefully about your posts!

 *** Children's Guidelines ( Children under 13 ):**

You are not allowed to register with Filmygyan or use the site unless you are at least 13 years old. Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important, which is why Filmygyan does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Filmygyan services from people under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to those under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Filmygyan services at any time or in any manner. If Filmygyan learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Filmygyan group sites without verified parental consent, then Filmygyan will take the necessary steps to delete this information.

 *** Being Anonymous**

The fact that you can send messages without other people knowing who you are is part of what makes Filmygyan unique and so much fun. It means that you can ask things that you might be too embarrassed or shy to say if anyone knew it was you. People are often bolder and more honest when they are anonymous, whether they're asking a question anonymously, or answering a question where they don't know who's asked it.

Some people don't like receiving things from people if they don't know who they are. So every member can choose not to receive questions from anonymous users on the 'Settings' page.

We all know that some people might abuse the option to be anonymous by being mean or by saying horrible things because they know you don't know who they are, but we will take steps to stop them from spoiling it for everyone else.

We may assist the Police or other law enforcement agencies with their requests to the extent required by law – otherwise, will not tell anyone who you are if you want to remain anonymous.

Occasionally a member may ask us if we can tell them the IP address of someone who sent them an anonymous message. Unfortunately, we are not able to give out that information.

 *** Cookies:**

Various methods are employed to gather this data. "Cookies" are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are "small strings of text" that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.

When user uses Filmygyan, our web server automatically records limited information about user interaction with our service i.e. “log data”, including the information which browser sends whenever user visits Filmygyan. This log data may include user computer’s connection to the internet, including User internet protocol address, browser type and settings, the date and time of user request. And how user used Filmygyan.

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific ads to your interests, and to save your login information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

 *** Security**

We have put in place appropriate security measures to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of information, including your personal information. We also use reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as secured servers using firewalls. Our technical experts at Filmygyan work hard to try and keep Filmygyan as safe and secure as we can.

We also impose appropriate requirements on our vendors/partners in order to protect the security and privacy of our users' confidential information.

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our website, our databases and records, you should know that no website or Internet transmission is completely secure and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. So, we strongly urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe (including your password) and to log out of your account after use – this will help keep your information secure. Remember, you decide what information you provide when chatting with people on Filmygyan.

Filmygyan use third party advertising companies to serve ads when any user visits the website. These advertising companies may use relevant information’s may or may not including your name, email address, contact number in order to show advertisements about products, goods and services of respective area of interest to the user.

 *** Third parties**

We don't sell or give out any personal information specifically about you to any third party. (If we were to sell our business, the buyer would take over all information that we have collected and kept.)

Filmygyan use third party advertising companies to serve ads when any user visits the website. These advertising companies may use relevant information’s may or may not including your name, email address, contact number in order to show advertisements about products, goods and services of respective area of interest to the user.

Filmygyan has the complete authority to remove third party websites / links if found inappropriate as per the Filmygyan Terms & Conditions defined.

 *** Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We may share general information that reflects the personal information you have provided to us or anything you have posted publicly (but which doesn’t identify you directly) with third parties for them to use for research and to deliver advertising about other products and services.

In particular, in relation to advertising, we may share your information with third-party advertising companies which we use to serve ads when you visit the Filmygyan site. These companies may use information about your visits to Filmygyan and other websites in order to advertise things which you might be interested in. For more information about this, please see our Terms of Use and Cookies Policy.

At Filmygyan we may cooperate with law enforcement enquiries to enforce any intellectual property or other rights. We may also share your personal information with government agencies, courts and/or other organisations who require it if we believe that it's necessary to protect our legal rights, or those of third parties and/or to comply with the law.

If there is any change of ownership in Filmygyan or any of our business, we may share your personal information with a prospective buyer and their advisors.

 *** Power to Change or Delete Account Data or Information and preferences:**

You can see and change your profile information at any time. Once you register, you will be able to change most of your personal information, including:

your name;

your country;

your contact email address;

your profile picture;

Email preferences; and

your password.

Please update your information if it changes as soon as you can by signing in to your account and following the screen prompts. We strongly recommend that you change your password every so often, to help keep things secure, as this will make it harder for people to hack into your account without your permission.

Users in certain countries are able to ask for a copy of the information we hold about them (for which, where allowed by law, we may charge a small fee). This needs to be done in writing and using our contact form: Feedback. We will let you know what else we need from you before we send you a copy of your personal information.

If any user wants to deactivate its respective account, user has to write us to admin@filmygyan.net. Our team will deactivate the user account including user all posts, comments, Expressions and other related information from public view. User can activate their account at any stage in future by writing us to admin@filmygyan.net our team will activate user account and restore all information including all posts, comments, Expressions and other related information.

 *** Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**

Filmygyan has the right to Change or amend its Privacy Policy with or without giving any prior notice to users. It is user’s responsibility to read privacy policy regularly and updates.

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically and this will be reflected by the "effective date" below. 

Date Last Modified: This Privacy Notice was last modified July 23, 2014.

 *** Contact us:**

If you have any question related to Privacy Policy of Filmygyan, Please use our contact form or write us to: admin@filmygyan.net 

For any Complain, feedback and Suggestions, please use our contact form or write us to: admin@filmygyan.net We will appreciate your feedback and suggestions and try to provide you the best service.
